export const questions = [
  [
    {
      category: "Music",
      id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b4e",
      correctAnswer: "Bob Marley and the Wailers",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Boney M.", "Gorillaz"],
      question: "Which band includes 'Bob Marley'?",
      tags: ["music"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "easy",
      regions: [],
    },
    {
      category: "Arts & Literature",
      id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950eff",
      correctAnswer: "Ursula K. Le Guin",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Stephen King", "Jack Vance", "George R. R. Martin"],
      question: "Which author wrote 'Earthsea series'?",
      tags: ["literature", "arts_and_literature"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "hard",
      regions: [],
    },
    {
      category: "Film & TV",
      id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950696",
      correctAnswer: "Tim Robbins",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Tim Roth", "Hugo Weaving", "Timothy Spall"],
      question:
        "Which actor has featued in films including Mystic River and Top Gun?",
      tags: ["acting", "film", "film_and_tv"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "hard",
      regions: [],
    },
    {
      category: "Music",
      id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b3f",
      correctAnswer: "Ha*Ash",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "The Pussycat Dolls",
        "Three 6 Mafia",
        "The Velvet Underground",
      ],
      question: "Which band includes 'Ashley Grace'?",
      tags: ["music"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "hard",
      regions: [],
    },
    {
      category: "History",
      id: "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951b8d",
      correctAnswer: "China",
      incorrectAnswers: ["India", "The USSR", "The USA"],
      question: "Which country invaded Tibet in 1950?",
      tags: ["history"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "medium",
      regions: [],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      category: "Geography",
      id: "6233885b0161109f922aac80",
      correctAnswer: "Lake Superior ",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Lake Baikal", "Lake Huron", "Lake Titicaca"],
      question: "Which Is The Largest Freshwater Lake by surface area?",
      tags: ["geography"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "hard",
      regions: [],
    },
    {
      category: "Geography",
      id: "62602e624b176d54800e3cd7",
      correctAnswer: "Wrocław",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Prague", "Hamburg", "Geneva"],
      question: "Which of these cities is in Poland?",
      tags: ["cities", "europe", "geography"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "medium",
      regions: [],
    },
    {
      category: "Film & TV",
      id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc11",
      correctAnswer: "Mrs. Robinson, you're trying to seduce me. Aren't you?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Soylent Green is people!",
        "Round up the usual suspects.",
        "Just keep swimming.",
      ],
      question: "Which of these quotes is from the film 'The Graduate'?",
      tags: ["quotes", "film", "film_and_tv"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "easy",
      regions: [],
    },
    {
      category: "Geography",
      id: "62602dcf014f58b5fc1a3fc6",
      correctAnswer: "Warsaw",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Helsinki", "Paris", "Düsseldorf"],
      question: "Which of these cities is in Poland?",
      tags: ["cities", "europe", "geography"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "medium",
      regions: [],
    },
    {
      category: "Society & Culture",
      id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd2c",
      correctAnswer: "Bertrand Russell",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Thomas Hobbes",
        "Jean-Jacques Rousseau",
        "Ludwig Wittgenstein",
      ],
      question:
        "Which philosopher famously said 'It is undesirable to believe a proposition when there is no ground whatever for supposing it true'?",
      tags: ["quotes", "philosophy", "society_and_culture"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "hard",
      regions: [],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      category: "Film & TV",
      id: "625698749da29df7b05f7288",
      correctAnswer: "Pepper Potts",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Valkyrie", "Eitri", "Wanda Maximoff"],
      question:
        "In the Marvel Cinematic Unvierse, which character is played by Gwyneth Paltrow?",
      tags: ["mcu", "film", "acting", "marvel", "comics", "film_and_tv"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "medium",
      regions: [],
    },
    {
      category: "Film & TV",
      id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950624",
      correctAnswer: "Toshirō Mifune",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Simon Pegg", "Terry O'Quinn", "Michael Keaton"],
      question:
        "Which actor has featued in films including Seven Samurai and Rashomon?",
      tags: ["film_and_tv"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "medium",
      regions: [],
    },
    {
      category: "Geography",
      id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff8c",
      correctAnswer: "Dublin",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Cork", "Limerick", "Galway"],
      question: "What is the capital of Ireland?",
      tags: ["capital_cities", "europe", "geography"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "medium",
      regions: [],
    },
    {
      category: "Geography",
      id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f9508da",
      correctAnswer: "Ivory Coast",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Ghana", "Togo", "Benin"],
      question: "Which of these countries borders Mali?",
      tags: ["africa", "geography"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "hard",
      regions: [],
    },
    {
      category: "Music",
      id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b1f",
      correctAnswer: "Spice Girls",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Editors", "Cradle of Filth", "The Sweet"],
      question: "Which band includes 'Victoria Beckham'?",
      tags: ["music"],
      type: "Multiple Choice",
      difficulty: "medium",
      regions: [],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b21",
    correctAnswer: "The Carpenters",
    incorrectAnswers: [
    "The Black Keys",
    "Three 6 Mafia",
    "The Velvet Underground"
    ],
    question: "Which American vocal duo released the studio album 'A Song for You'?",
    tags: [
    "music"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [ ]
    },
    {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f950fea",
    correctAnswer: "Tungsten",
    incorrectAnswers: [
    "Cobalt",
    "Nickel",
    "Titanium"
    ],
    question: "Which metal has the chemical element W?",
    tags: [
    "science"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [ ]
    },
    {
    category: "Music",
    id: "625064e7e12f6dec240bdfd6",
    correctAnswer: "Two of Hearts",
    incorrectAnswers: [
    "Heart And Soul",
    "Tainted Love",
    "Lovin' You"
    ],
    question: "Stacey Q had a one hit wonder in 1986 with which song?",
    tags: [
    "songs",
    "one_hit_wonders",
    "music"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [ ]
    },
    {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f28",
    correctAnswer: "Hans Christian Andersen",
    incorrectAnswers: [
    "Beatrix Potter",
    "Søren Kierkegaard",
    "Oscar Wilde"
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Snow Queen'?",
    tags: [
    "childrens_literature",
    "literature",
    "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [ ]
    },
    {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951be2",
    correctAnswer: "116 Years",
    incorrectAnswers: [
    "100 Years",
    "38 Minutes",
    "94 Years"
    ],
    question: "How Long Did The 100 Years War Last?",
    tags: [
    "history"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [ ]
    }
    ],
        
];
